Huy Nguyen

. +61 466 653 902

☑ huynguyenaui@gmail.com

huynguyen.space

in linkedin.com/in/huy-nguyen-454a6016a

About Me

I'm a passionate individual and an avid learner with professional developer experience. I thrive on tackling interesting and difficult challenges.

Skills

- C# (.NET Core 3.1), SQL (MSSQL, MySQL), Python, PHP, JS, Bash, Powershell
- Azure, Docker
- · Confluence, Jira
- Windows, Linux

Work Experience

IT Specialist

EnergyLocals | Sep 2020 to present

- Developed an automated processes to download, process, and import millions of rows from AEMO settlements weekly.
- Deployed Azure resources to handle AEMO settlements.
- Written tutorials and documented common IT issues on Confluence.

Graduate IT Specialist

EnergyLocals | Sep 2019 to Sep 2020

- Developed a full-stack white-labeled website used by many companies.
- Automated tasks that took hours when performed manually.
- Written Python, Powershell, and Bash scripts to backup and process data weekly.
- Deploy and maintain cloud servers required for business and IT day-to-day activities.
- Produced SQL scripts to assist in business and government reporting.

Passions

Lox Lang

craftinginterpreters.com

- Learn to implement a fully featured scripting language.
- My goal is to learn the foundations of developing a programming language in order to better understand how a computer works.

Fast Al

fast.ai

- A deep learning library that aims to give experts in other fields who don't have strong programming skills the ability to leverage the power of Al.
- My goal is to be familiar with the basic concepts of deep learning and general data science.

Education

Computer and Network Engineering (Honours)

RMIT | 2016 to 2020